# ZOEY LOGAN

Detail-orientated senior accounting manager with more than eight years of experience in analyzing financial information and managing people. Proven track record of seeing projects (123)456-7890 through to completion within deadlines and with 100% accuracy. Goal-orientated and self-motivated professional who is able to work independently or as part of a team.

123 Main Street, Miami, FL 12345 Z.loga n@yo u rem ai I .com

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### SENIOR ACCOUNTING MANAGER

ABC Corporation, Miami, FL September 2017 - Present

- Oversee a tea m of 15 acco u nti n g s pecia 1 i sts w ho a re respo nsi ble for pay ro 11,
  financial reports, accounts receivable, and billing
- Ana lyze quarterly and monthly financials and create a detailed report to present to co m pa ny exec utives
- Workoncost reduction ideas
- Ensure the company financials comply with state and federal laws
- Prepare all documentation required for annual external audits
- Present budget forecasts to senior management
- Maintaina 11 accounting ledgers

## ASSISTANT ACCOUNTING MANAGER

Imagination Retail, Miami, FL June 2012 - August 2017

- Checked the work of four accounting specialists and reported any discrepancies to the senior accounting manager
- Identified methods of reducing costs and managed to reduce company expenses by 27%
- Assisted the senior accounting manager in creating financial reports for senior management
- Performed research on operational data and financial results

### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Science in Accounting

The University Of Miami, Miami, FI September2006- June 2010

Master of Business Administration The University Of Miami, Miami, FI Septem ber 2006 - June 2012

### **KEY SKILLS**

- Financial auditing
- Time management
- Budget tracking
- Analytical skills
- Leadership